Guide to the Ladyslipper, Inc. Records, 1965-2011 and undated RL.10140
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Series, 1972-2011; 3
  - Director's Office Files subseries, 1972-2011; 3.4
    - CYE Uncommitted Report, 9/2000, 1 folders (Box 108)
    - WILD Insurance, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 108)
    - Women in Music/Chicago Thelma Norris, 1977-1978; 1 folders (Box 108)
    - Women's Pavillion, 1972; 1 folders (Box 108)
- Retail Series, 1976-2006; 4
  - Retail Vendor Files subseries, 1976-1998; 4.1
    - ABA Record Distributors, 1985-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Abzula Productions (Abbe Lyons), 1990; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - A. Howl/Julia Haines, 1988-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Alzacar Records/Silo, 1981-1988; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - American Gramaphone, 1989-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - American Melody, 1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Andy's Front Hall, 1986-1989; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Anne Feeney, 1986-1988; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Another Sundown Publishing, 1988-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Another Printshop, 1988-1989; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Ariel Records, 1988-1992; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Aronsound, 1986-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Aro Veno, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Art Gil (Cynthia Watts), 1990; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Artwear Concepts, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Aurora/Jane Howard, 1989-1990; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Barely Lace, 1989-1993; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Bay Records, 1978-1988; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Bet-Car, 1982-1989; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Beth Scalet, 1989-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Big Pond, 1982-1985; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Biograph, 1977-1989; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - BKM Associates, 1985-1986; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Blue Angel, 1984-1986; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Brame Specialty Co., 1982-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Brave Dog, 1988; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Capriccio Records, 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Carole Anne Burris, 1989-1992; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Carthage Records, 1985-1992; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - CD Presents, 1986-1987; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - CD Willie's, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Celestial Harmonies, 1986-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Celebrity Home Entertainment, 1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - CEMA Distribution (2 folders), 1984-1991 (Box 81)
    - Chameleon Music Group, 1988-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - CheXpress, 1990; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Choral Majority, 1982-1987; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Collector Records, 1982-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - The Coronet Recording Co., 1984-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Cynthia Watts, 1988; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Dancing Shoes Music, 1985-1989; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Danielle Boutet, 1986-1989; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Discovery Systems, 1987-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Dotti Moseley, 1984-1989; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Duro-test Lighting, 1989-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Dyveke Spino, 1985-1989; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Earth Books, 1988-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Earwig Records, 1987-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Echo, Inc., 1986; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Edge of Wonder, 1988-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Emerald Web, 1987-1989; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Emma Truck, 1986-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Eye in Eye, 1986-1990; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Fantasy Records, 1977-1987; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Fast Folk Musical Magazine, 1984-1987; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Festival Records, 1985-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Fidelity Products, 1979-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Pilagree Deep/Sue Robbins, 1986-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Flash Silvermoon, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Flat Town Music Co., 1988-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Flying Fish, 1978-1989; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Forrest/Gaulke/Maberry, 1988-1989; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Fran Avni, 1987-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Fresh Fruit, 1984-1988; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Fuse Music, 1985-1989; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Producciones Gad, Inc., 1988-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Glen Canyon, 1984-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Global Industrial Equipment, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Gold Castle Records, 1988-1989; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Golden Glow, 1986-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Greenwoods Industrial Park, 1979-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Great Leap, 1985-1988; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - GRW Associates, Inc., 1989; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Gryphon, 1987-1989; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Global Village, 1988-1990; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Hands on Productions, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Haresuite, 1983-1989; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Harper Collins, 1984-1991; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Helaine Victoria, 1979-1989; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Hummingbird Productions, 1984-1990; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Hunter Davis, 1982-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - International Book & Record Distributors, 1981-1988; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - IJE, 1985-1987; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Indian House Records, 1978-1989; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Indipop Music Limited, 1985-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Intercon, 1988-1990; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - International Productions, 1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - JEJ Musical Enterprises, Ltd., 1986-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Magi Crafts, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Jan Phillips, 1988-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Jeffmajors & Yasmeen, 1987-1990; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Jennifer Justice, 1986-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Jerusalem Media Workshop, 1986-1987; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Jesse X, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Joan Marie McMillen, 1990-1992; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Judith Barr, 1990; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Karen Goldberg, 1987-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Kid's Records, 1985-1987; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Kona Kai Distribution Company, 1983-1988; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Kripalu Shop, 1986-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Labrys, 1983-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Land-O-Newts, 1987-1990; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Laughing Out Loud Music/Peggy Ward, 1990; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Leading Edge Review, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Lee Underwood, 1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Lemonside Records, 1987-1989; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Lifeline, 1988-1990; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Lilah/Rockduster Records, 1989-1990; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Living Room Productions, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Loulan Productions, 1987-1990; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Lovely Communications, 1982-1992; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Demi-Soeurs, 1991-1992; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Lullaby Lady, 1985-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Magical Music Express, 1987-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Maia, 1988-1989; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Mama-T Artists/The Folktellers, 1989-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Marie Rhines, 1984; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Marie Riley, 1985-1990; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Marilyn Ries, 1986-1987; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Marimolin, 1988-1989; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Mark Weigle, 1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Marnie Hall, 1982-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Mary Records, 1977-1990; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Mary Shields, 1989-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Masterworks Chorale, 1986-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Mastodon/Chris Johnston, 1988-1989; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Mass Coaltion of Battered Women Services, 1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Mecca Normal, 1987; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Mercury Films, 1990; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Metromusic (2 folders), 1988-1991 (Box 82)
    - Miss Jackie, 1982-1987; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Minnesota Public Radio, 1986; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Moss Music Group, 1979-1990; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - M. Susan Ray, 1986-1987; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Muddy Paws, 1990-1992; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Master Your Mind, 1988-1992; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Nancy Vogl, 1989; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Narada, 1985-1992; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Nemeton/Constance Bereus, 1989-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - New World, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Nicaragua Information Center, 1986; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Nick Mathis, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Night Vision Productions Inc., 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Wes/Night Vision, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - New Music Distribution Service, 1988; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - North Country Distributors, 1985-1990; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - North State Video, 1988; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Number Crunchers, Inc., 1987-1989; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - National Women's Studies Association, 1986-1988; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Old Homestead, 1983-1991; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Oracle, 1986; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Orion Master Recordings, 1985-1987; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Ova, 1980-1989; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Ova Retorts, 1983-1987; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Pacific Lists, 1991; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Panoramic Sound, 1988; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Parallax Press, 1988-1993; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Performing Arts Press, 1984-1989; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Patience & Adventures Musicworks, 1986-1991; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Patty Zeitlin, 1987-1989; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Pearls of Laughter, 1988-1989; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Pegajosa Productions, 1988-1989; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Perfect Pitch, 1989-1991; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Phyllis Ward, 1980-1989; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Pickwick Music Group, Inc., 1989; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - PM Records, 1976-1988; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Poshek Productions, 1989-1991; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Potentials Unlimited, 1989-1990; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Private Music, 1987-1991; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Rainbow Morning Music, 1983-1988; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Rainbow Planet, 1987-1989; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Rainbow Snake, 1983-1989; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Raindreaming Productions, 1989-1991; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Chrysalis Distributing, 1988; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Ray Mar, 1985-1986; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Record Wide Distribution, 1983-1990; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Records on Wheels, 1982-1987; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Red Rose Gallery, 1987-1989; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Redwood Recores, 1989-1992; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Regulator Press, 1977-1990; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Relic Records, 1985-1988; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Righteous Mothers, 1984-1989; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Riverlark Music, 1982-1989; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Rosemary Silversteen, 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Ross Ellis, 1984-1990; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Rounder Records, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Rounder Catalogs, 1979-1988; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Rough Trade, 1981-1991; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Run River Records, 1989-1990; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Sabia, 1982-1990; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Schroeder Music Company, 1976-1985; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Seal Press, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Seventh Generation, 1989-1990; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Silo Inc., 1983-1988; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Silver Lining, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Smile Herb Shop, 1989; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Sonic Atmospheres, 1985-1989; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Sound Environment, 1978-1990; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Sound RX, 1988-1991; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Stasia Co., 1989-1990; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Straker's, 1983-1991; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Stratham Fields Productions, 1988-1989; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Subterranean Records, 1986-1990; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Sumitra Records, 1984-1990; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Syracuse University Press, 1987-1989; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Suresha, 1988-1989; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Surplus Record & Tape, 1991; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Susanne Paris, 1985-1986; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Tara Publications, 1984-1989; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Tendre, 1987-1988; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Thrival Productions, 1988-1990; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Thunderhoney, 1987-1989; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Transister, 1988-1989; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Treena Productions, 1987-1991; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Troubadour Records, 1987-1991; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Uncle Ruthie Suell, 1985-1989; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Universal Record Distributing Co.`, 1990-1992; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Universal Printing and Publishing, 1983-1998; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Vallen Productions, 1988; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Vaughn Electric Company, 1990; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Vintage Records, 1991; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Wheel & Dheel, 1986-1988; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Wild Bills, 1986-1987; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Windham Hill (2 folders), 1987-1990 (Box 84)
    - Witch-A-Way/Shekhinah Mountainwater, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - WMG, Inc., 1990-1993; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Woods Music & Books, 1983-1991; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Woody Simmons, 1989; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Kim Oswalt/Woofus Records, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Yansa Music, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Z-Band/Helene Christopher, 1989-1990; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - ZBS, 1991; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Ana Laforest, 1988-1991; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Zuleikha, 1988-1990; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Wholesale Files
      - The Alternative Shop, 1988-1989; 1 folders (Box 84)
      - Ampersound, 1992; 1 folders (Box 84)
      - An Die Musik, Inc., 1991-1993; 1 folders (Box 84)
      - Are Press, 1990-1993; 1 folders (Box 84)
      - Body Mind & Soul, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 84)
      - Bold Print, 1986-1994; 1 folders (Box 84)
      - Chosen Books, 1984-1990; 1 folders (Box 84)
      - Clairelight, 1986-1995; 1 folders (Box 84)
      - Fan the Flames, 1981-1996; 1 folders (Box 84)
      - Infinite Blue, 1989-1990; 1 folders (Box 84)
      - Jurus Ltd., 1994; 1 folders (Box 84)
      - Marianne Kalin, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 84)
      - LeFon, Inc., 1994; 1 folders (Box 84)
      - Magical Transformations, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 84)
      - NARAL, 1989-1991; 1 folders (Box 84)
      - Paradigm, 1988-1996; 1 folders (Box 84)
      - Peaches Worksheets, 1 folders (Box 84)
  - Subdistribution Files and Financial Reports subseries, 1976-1994; 4.2
    - Adrienne Torf, 1985-1986; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Ars Pro Feminina-77 retorts, 1977-1986; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Baker & Taylor, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Cattail Music, 1983-1986; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Cimirron/Rainbird Records, 1989-1994; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Cityscape, 1984-1988; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Gentle Wind Retorts, 1983-1986; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Happy Onion, 1985-1988; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Harper & Row Publishers Inc., 1991-1993; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Icebergg Records, 1989-1992; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Invincible Records G.R.D. Real Time, 1984-1987; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Jane Siberry, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Judy Mowati Dist., 1982; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Karen Mackay-West Virginia Woman, 1985-1988; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Kicking Mule Records, 1981-1986; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Lady Reason Retorts, 1986-1990; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - "Listen To This Music", 1982-1983; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Llewellyn Publications, 1986-1991; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Malaprop's Bookstore, 1984-1986; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Mary Watkins, 1985; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Meridian-LF's attempt to reconcile and pay balance, 1987-1991; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Mimi Fox, 1988-1993; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - MTS-Tower-DC, 1984-1986; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Music Video Distributors, 1989; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Narada, 1985-1988; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - New World Productions, 1986-1987; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - New Words, 1979-1986; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Old Lady Blue Jeans-Linda Shear, 1977-1984; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Olivia Records, 1978-1987; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Origami Retorts, 1982-1986; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Pearls of Laughter, 1987-1989; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Peggy Seeger, 1983; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Philo, 1979 -1984; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Pleiades Records, 1976-1994; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Rainbow Blossom, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Rainbow of Crystals, 1989-1990; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Randy's Rainbow World, 1989-1990; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Raven, 1989-1994; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Rebecca Retorts, 1983-1986; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Record Bar, 1988-1995; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Records in Such, 1994; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Redwood Records (2 folders), 1976-1989 (Box 85)
    - Relaxation Store, 1992; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Renaissance Books, 1987-1993; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Robin Flower, 1986-1987; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Robin Tyler, 1986-1989; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Rounder Invoices Pulled for Payment Verification, 1987-1993; 1 folders (Box 85)
  - Retail Files from Reggae Dodson's Office subseries, 1977-1994; 4.3
    - Assorted Information from Media Production Companies, 1992-1999; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Artists LS Sub-Distributes, 1993; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - CD Packaging: Environmentally Good! (Jewel Box Alternatives), 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Miscellaneous Letters from LS (4 folders), 1988-1993 (Box 101)
    - CD Packaging: Environmentally Correct, 1990-1994; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Europadisc CD Manu., 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Carolina Cassette Distribs, 1989-1990; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Intercontinental Communication Corporation, 1991; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Radio Playlists: Check Against Master & Add If Not On, 1977-1987; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Radio, 1 folders (Box 101)
    - New Age Radio, 1984-1986; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - More ARP Radio Work--Hearts of Space, etc., 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Radio Stations-respones to LR 103, 1984-1987; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Stations That Gave Kay--ARP Play. Labels, 1987-1989; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Stations Sending Playlists LR103 Not On, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Josh's 1st List, not used for LR 201, 1988; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Radio Stations That Played Our Stuff, 1985-1988; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - AEI, 1988; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Radio Station Databases, 1988; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Olivia's Radio List, 1 folders (Box 101)
    - National Media--Folk, Rock, Misc., 1985-1987; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - National Women's /Gay Press Ad Rates, 1985-1986; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Ken Roseman PO Box 744, 1985-1987; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Debbie Fier Radio & Press Lists, 1984; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Trades Updates, 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Billboard, 1986; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Schwann, 1986; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Phonolog, 1 folders (Box 101)
    - In-Territory Press, 1985-1987; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - International Publications, 1986; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Potnetial Advertisers: stores, papers, labels, Xerox labels, etc., 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Sapphile-Community Cardpack, 1 folders (Box 101)
    - New Age Mags-Ad Rates, 1985-1989; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Continuity Publishing, 1988; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Digital Audio, 1 folders (Box 101)
    - AIDS Research, 1987-1990; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - New Age Catalogs, 1987-1988; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Heartsong Review, 1986-1987; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - N.A. Media Rates, 1981-1986; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - East-West Journals- AD, 1984; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - The National Network, 1985; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - National Resource-AD, 1985; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - New Age Journal, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - New Age Media Resource Directory, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Whole Life Times, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - CD Boxes, 1987; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Daio-Kosan, 1989; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - Diskmakers-CD Stuff, 1987; 1 folders (Box 101)
    - CD Exploration, 1985-1988; 1 folders (Box 101)
  - Clippings from Reggae Dodson's Office subseries, 1985-2006; 4.4
    - Miscellaneous Magazines (3 folders), 1985-1994 (Box 102)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Magazines about Madonna, 1986-1989; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Almighty Records, 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Alive!, 1993-1998; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Bar Code Stuff, 1995; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - BMG, 1994; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - BMG Music Club, 1995; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Booking Workshop Info., 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Caroline Aiken, 1996; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Circles Mag., 1997; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - PCC Compact Classics, 1996; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Discovery/Venture Marketing, 1993-1995; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Dove Audio, 1994; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Edwina Lee Tyler Cassette Production, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Epulse, 2006; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Feather Boa, 1994; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Flying Fish, 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Holly Stock-concert, 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Ice Mag, 1999; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - K-Tel, 1996-1997; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - KABA, 1991-1993; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Lea, 1993-1996; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - LR 103, 1992-2002; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - LR 106CS, 1996; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - LR 108, 1990-2001; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - LR 109, 1993-1998; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - LR 111 Amazon, 1992-1998; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - LR 112, 1995-1999; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - LR 113, 1993; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - LR 114 "Drum Call", 1994-1998; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - LR 115, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - LR 116 "Shape Shifters", 1995-2000; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - LR 117, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - LR 118, 1998-2001; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - LR 1200, 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Rhiannon LR 202, 1990-1999; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - LR 203 & 204, 1993-1998; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Maggie's Music, 1997; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Mesa-Blue Moon, 1995; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Navarre, 1997; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Oak Street, 1989; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Out Spoken Video, 1994; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Random Home, 1994; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Seventh Wave, 1996; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Simon & Schuster Paramount Publish, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - SPV Germany, 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Tent (Light Dome), 1996; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Two Nice Girls, 1992; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Willow Tree, 1990; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Windham Hill, 1996-2000; 1 folders (Box 102)
    - Wolfe Video, 1994-1996; 1 folders (Box 102)
  - Wholesale Accounts subseries, 1980-1995; 4.5
    - About Us Books, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Accent On Music, 1991; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Acoustic Collage, 1991; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - ADIFFE, 1994; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Ageless Art, 1993; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - A Healing Place, 1992; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Akasha Books, 1992-1994; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Akashik Books, 1991; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Alaska Women's Books, 1986-1994; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Albums on the Hill, 1992; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - The Alchemist, 1993; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Aloha Village Store, 1993; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Alpenglow, 1991; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - The American Treasury, 1993; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - ANB Music/Human Condition, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - A New Dawn, 1992; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Angel de las Flores, 1993; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Angelic Bookworm, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Anne Wigmore Institute, 1993; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Anonymously Yours, 1991-1994; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - A Novel Experience, 1991-1992; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Anything Under the Moon, 1992-1994; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - The Arbor Moon, 1991-1994; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Ariadne Books, 1992; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Aries Arts, 1991; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Armadillo Mountain, 1987-1991; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Artemis Promotions, 1991; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Ashkess Earth Medicine, 1994; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Athena's Attic, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Atlantis Center and Bookshop, 1994; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Aum-Nee Crystals and Books, 1990; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Avalon, the Inner-Isle, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 103)
    - Ave Maria & Co, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 103)